bmw-sg.com 2013-11-25

# Privacy Policy | BMW.SG

**To protect your privacy, Zeta Media Pte Ltd (http://www.bmw-sg.com) follows the following principles for member privacy and data protection.**

**DISCLAIMER:** Zeta Media Pte Ltd (http://www.bmw-sg.com) is in no way sponsored, endorsed or affiliated by or with BMW NA / BMW AG or any of it's subsidiaries or vendors (which includes Performance Motors Limited, Singapore) . Zeta Media Pte Ltd (http://www.bmw-sg.com) recognizes that "BMW", the roundel and various model numbers are registered trademarks of BMW AG.

**WHY WE OBTAIN INFORMATION  
**We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you create a new user profile on the site to use specific features available only to registered users.

The primary reason we obtain this information is to make the site easier for you to use by not having you enter information more than once. We may also periodically use your information to alert you to updated information and other new services from www.bmw-sg.com.

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of bmw-sg.com. But you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration.

**REGISTERED USER PROFILES  
**When you register, your information is protected by use of a password which you select. Each person who registers must have a unique email address and user name. Duplicate profiles using the same email address or user name are not permitted. We highly recommend that you select a password which is neither common or known to others. We encourage you to NOT use information such as your Social Security Number, Phone Number or Date of Birth as your password.

If you are a previous registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may only obtain it by email using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the link on any login page to request your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means.

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time. By following the "my profile" link provided on our system, you may view and edit personal information you have already given us. You may also elect to receive or discontinue receiving any email newsletters we may choose to distribute periodically. Once you register, you won't need to do it again. Wherever you go on http://bmw-sg.com, your information stays with you.

The following are the terms of the privacy statement of Zeta Media Pte Ltd(http://www.bmw-sg.com) Or ("Zeta Media Pte Ltd") regarding use of Zeta Media Pte Ltd's web site www.bmw-sg.com ("The Site"). 

Zeta Media Pte Ltd collects certain information in various ways from The Site and uses that information in various ways. Sensitive information such as credit card numbers and account numbers are encrypted and are not intentionally shared with any other parties but Zeta Media Pte Ltd will not be liable for any inadvertent disclosure. Zeta Media Pte Ltd may, however, use or provide to third parties statistics about members, traffic patterns and related information including but not limited to personally identifying information such as names, addresses, emails and the like as well as information gathered from the use of "cookie" or other technologies, whether from advertisements on The Site or otherwise. However, such information will not intentionally include such credit card information or account numbers except for the limited purpose of collecting payments, communicating with credit card companies and the like but Zeta Media Pte Ltd will not be liable for any inadvertent disclosure. Such information may be used by Zeta Media Pte Ltd in the aggregate or individually and may be combined with other information and may be in connection with marketing of such information or as part of a transaction related to any aspect of the business of Zeta Media Pte Ltd including but not limited to sales, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies and the like. You agree that Zeta Media Pte Ltd may use and provide to third parties the said information that you provide except as indicated. If you do not agree with the provisions of this paragraph, you should not provide any information to Zeta Media Pte Ltd.

**Partnerships, Affiliates, Advertisers and Other Links** : Through Zeta Media Pte Ltd you may be introduced to a variety of third-party vendors and sites. The privacy polices of these third parties are not under Zeta Media Pte Ltd's control and may differ from Zeta Media Pte Ltd's and you should read the privacy policies of those vendors carefully. The use of any information that you may provide to any third party, or the use of "cookie" technology by any third party, will be governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site that you are visiting. In some cases these third parties may share the information that they collect about you with Zeta Media Pte Ltd. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information you are providing on another site, Zeta Media Pte Ltd recommends that you contact that site directly for more information and review their privacy policy. Zeta Media Pte Ltd is not now and never will be responsible for the actions of such third parties in any manner whatsoever, including but not limited to any violation of such privacy policies or otherwise.

Zeta Media Pte Ltd may use information from or provide information to such third parties including but not limited to statistics about members, traffic patterns and related information including but not limited to personally identifying information such as names, addresses, emails and the like as well as information gathered from the use of "cookie" or other technologies, whether from advertisements on The Site or otherwise but will not intentionally include such credit card information or account numbers, except as set forth above but Zeta Media Pte Ltd will not be liable for any inadvertent disclosure. Such information may be used by Zeta Media Pte Ltd in the aggregate or individually and may be combined with other information and may be in connection with marketing of such information or as part of a transaction related to any aspect of the business of Zeta Media Pte Ltd including but not limited to sales, mergers, acquisitions, bankruptcies and the like. You agree that Zeta Media Pte Ltd may use and provide to such third parties the said information that you provide except as indicated. If you do not agree with the provisions of this paragraph, you should not provide any information to Zeta Media Pte Ltd.

**Third Party Advertising:** We use Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies:** In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Your Rights to Opt Out and Change or Delete Your Information:** If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other correspondence related to Zeta Media Pte Ltd's or third parties' promotions or products, or you do not wish to have Zeta Media Pte Ltd be entitled to use the information that Zeta Media Pte Ltd may use as indicated in this statement, simply indicate your preference when you are asked to provide the information or send Zeta Media Pte Ltd email at the address indicated below.

****Zeta Media Pte Ltd's**  Rights To Change.** Zeta Media Pte Ltd may change this privacy statement or any aspect of it by publicly posting such changes on The Site but without any individual notice to you. Notwithstanding anything else in this privacy statement, Zeta Media Pte Ltd may release information when it believes that such release is reasonably necessary to (1) comply with law, (2) enforce or apply terms of any of agreement between you and Zeta Media Pte Ltd or (3) protect the rights, property or safety of Zeta Media Pte Ltd, other users, or others.

**General Provisions.** Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example on message boards, through email, or in chat areas), that information can be collected and used by Zeta Media Pte Ltd and by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages.

**Contact Information:**

Via email: [admin@bmw-sg.com](http://www.cloudflare.com/email-protection#5233363f3b3c12303f257f21357c313d3f)
